Guide to the Harry Randall: Fifteenth International Brigade Films and Photographs ALBA.PHOTO.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series B: Individual Portraits, September 1937-September 1938
  - Photo Unit #: B262 Abraham Lewis, Brigade Commissariat, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0955)
  - Photo Unit #: B263 Antony B. Drossel, Brigade Photographer, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0956)
  - Photo Unit #: B264 William Frame, Brigade Intendencia, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0683)
  - Photo Unit #: B267 Harry Lichter, Commissariat, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0684)
  - Photo Unit #: B272 Major Germina Galleani, 15th Brigade Staff, Alcorisa, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1295)
  - Photo Unit #: B273 Captain Raphael Brage, Valverde, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0957)
  - Photo Unit #: B276 Lieutenant Claudio Villanueva, Commanding 59th Battalion (previously, in 1937, Lincoln-Washington Battalion) (Portuguese), Mar 1938 (Item 11-0958)
  - Photo Unit #: B277 Ramon Castel, Company 2, 59th Battalion, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0959)
  - Photo Unit #: B278 Jose Santana, Company 2, 59th Battalion, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0960)
  - Photo Unit #: B280 Lieutenant William Digges, 15th International Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Mar 1938 (Item 11-0963)
  - Photo Unit #: B281 Lieutenant Steve Tsermengas, 15th International Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Mar 1938 (Item 11-0964)
  - Photo Unit #: B284 Captain Francisco Capellino Gil, E. Bat. [?], Mar 1938 (Item 11-0961)
  - Photo Unit #: B285 Captain Domingo Morales, Company 3, British Battalion, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0962)
  - Photo Unit #: B287 [?] Goerk, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0965)
  - Photo Unit #: B289 Nickolay [?], Acting Brigade Commander [Image missing], Mar 1938 (Item 11-1852)
  - Photo Unit #: B290 Louis Elder, 15th International Brigade office, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0966)
  - Photo Unit #: B292 Rudolf J. Corbin, Brigade Scout, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0967)
  - Photo Unit #: B293 Joe Greenstein, Auto Park (responsable) [Image missing], Mar 1938 (Item 11-1853)
  - Photo Unit #: B294 Michael Shanzky, first aid, Lincoln-Washington, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0005)
  - Photo Unit #: B295 Walter O'Kane, Transmiciones [Transmissions], Nov 1937 (Item 11-0006)
  - Photo Unit #: B296 Elhanon Winchester Bridges, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0007)
  - Photo Unit #: B297 Gustav Kleiger, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0008)
  - Photo Unit #: B299 Clyde Taylor, MacKenzie-Papineau, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0009)
  - Photo Unit #: B302 William Frame, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0118)
  - Photo Unit #: B303 William Frame, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0119)
  - Photo Unit #: B304 Norman Berkowitz, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0120)
  - Photo Unit #: B305 Peter Schultz, Auto Park, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0968)
  - Photo Unit #: B306 Captain Herman Hernandez, Commander of 59th Battalion, undated (Item 11-1824)
  - Photo Unit #: B307 Sidney Bassin, Auto Park, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0685)
    Available Formats: Original Negative; Copy Negative
  - Photo Unit #: B308 Sidney Bassin, Auto Park, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0686)
  - Photo Unit #: B310 Harry Randall, Brigade Photographer, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0010)
  - Photo Unit #: B311 José María Sastre, 35th Division Commissar, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1297)
    (Moscow Number: 5/188/97)
  - Photo Unit #: B312 Earl Steward of MacKenzie-Papineau, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0011)
  - Photo Unit #: B314 Abraham Lewis of Commissariat, Jan 1938 (Item 11-0012)
  - Photo Unit #: B315 Alexander Goldberg, Commissar of Sanidad [Health], 15th International Brigade, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0121)
  - Photo Unit #: B316 Major Robert Merriman, Chief of Staff, 15th International Brigade, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0122)
  - Photo Unit #: B318 Robert (Red) Prange, Transmiciones [Transmissions], MacKenzie-Papineau, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0123)
  - Photo Unit #: B319 Maurice Simon, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0124)
  - Photo Unit #: B320 Joseph Roffman, Lincoln-Washington, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0125)
  - Photo Unit #: B321 Joseph Roffman, Lincoln-Washington, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0126)
  - Photo Unit #: B324 Eluard Luchell McDaniels, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0127)
  - Photo Unit #: B325 Andrew Mitchell, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0128)
  - Photo Unit #: B327 [Soldier, unidentified], Mar 1938 (Item 11-0129)
  - Photo Unit #: B328 Ernest Kozlowsky (?) in Auto Park, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0013)
  - Photo Unit #: B329 Joseph Greenstein, Auto Park, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0014)
  - Photo Unit #: B331 Hyman Chesler, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0015)
  - Photo Unit #: B332 Crawford Morgan, Auto Park, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0130)
  - Photo Unit #: B333 Herman (Gabby) Klein, oficina [?], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0131)
  - Photo Unit #: B335 John Gates, Brigade Commissar, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0132)
  - Photo Unit #: B336 Emanuel Arkas, Auto Park, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0133)
  - Photo Unit #: B337 Peter Schultz, Auto Park, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0134)
  - Photo Unit #: B338 Thomas Norton, Topography, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0135)
  - Photo Unit #: B339 Leo Solodkin, Topography, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0136)
  - Photo Unit #: B342 Louis Stoloff, Transmiciones [Transmissions], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0137)
  - Photo Unit #: B344 Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, Commander, 15th International Brigade, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0138)
  - Photo Unit #: B346 Matti Mattson, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0139)
  - Photo Unit #: B347 Matti Mattson, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0140)
  - Photo Unit #: B348 Ivan Rujevcic, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0141)
  - Photo Unit #: B349 Joseph Brandt, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0142)
  - Photo Unit #: B350 Joseph Brandt, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0143)
  - Photo Unit #: B351 Daniel Pasternack, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0144)
  - Photo Unit #: B352 William Baker, Auto Park, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0145)
  - Photo Unit #: B353 Robert Cummins, Brigade runner, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0146)
  - Photo Unit #: B354 Isadore Levitt [alias Jack Cooper], Brigade Machine-Gunner Company, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0147)
  - Photo Unit #: B355 Frank Dorsey, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0148)
  - Photo Unit #: B357 Lieutenant Aaron Lopoff, Adjuntant, Lincoln-Washington, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0149)
  - Photo Unit #: B358 George Watt, Commissar, Lincoln-Washington, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0150)
  - Photo Unit #: B359 Benny Brostoff, Practicante, Lincoln-Washington, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0151)
  - Photo Unit #: B361 [Soldier holding rifle], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0152)
  - Photo Unit #: B362 Anthony Rizzo, Lincoln-Washington, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0153)
  - Photo Unit #: B363 Paul Meleschuk of Auto Park [posing with rifle and bayonet], Apr 1938 (Item 11-1298)
  - Photo Unit #: B365 William Buchkowski, MacKenzie-Papineau, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0154)
  - Photo Unit #: B367 Simon Leinoff, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0155)
  - Photo Unit #: B368 Mayor Edward Cecil Smith, Chief, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1299)
  - Photo Unit #: B369 Edward Cecil Smith, Chief, MacKenzie-Papineau, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0156)
  - Photo Unit #: B370 Captain John Simon, Doctor, British Battalion, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0157)
  - Photo Unit #: B372 William Chega, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0158)
  - Photo Unit #: B374 Ione Siegel, Auto Park chauffeur, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0159)
  - Photo Unit #: B375 Ione Siegel, Auto Park chauffeur, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0160)
  - Photo Unit #: B376 Captain Milton Wolff, Lincoln-Washington, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0161)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/33)
  - Photo Unit #: B379 Captain Max Milman, Adjuntant, 59th Battalion (Argentine), Apr 1938 (Item 11-0162)
  - Photo Unit #: B380 Angel Tsareff, 2nd Company Commissar, 59th Battalion (Argentine), Apr 1938 (Item 11-0163)
  - Photo Unit #: B381 Jacob Liffland, topographer, Lincoln-Washington, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0164)
  - Photo Unit #: B382 Jacob Liffland, topographer, Lincoln-Washington, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0165)
  - Photo Unit #: B383 Yale Stuart, Lincoln-Washington, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0166)
  - Photo Unit #: B385 Sergeant Joseph Taylor, Lincoln-Washington activist, especially distinguished, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0167)
  - Photo Unit #: B391 Nicolas Kurkuliotis, Lincoln-Washington, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0168)
  - Photo Unit #: B392 Michael Athanasiades, Lincoln-Washington, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0169)
  - Photo Unit #: B393 Thomas O'Flaherty, Lincoln-Washington activist, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0170)
  - Photo Unit #: B394 Valentin Koppel, Lincoln-Washington activist, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0171)
  - Photo Unit #: B395 [Lincoln-Washington activist (?)], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0172)
  - Photo Unit #: B396 Stanley Vernon, Lincoln-Washington activist, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0173)
  - Photo Unit #: B397 Sergeant Roy Sheehan, Lincoln-Washington activist, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0174)
  - Photo Unit #: B398 Ernest Kozlowsky (?), Lincoln-Washington activist, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0175)
  - Photo Unit #: B399 Alvah Bessie, Lincoln-Washington activist, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0176)
  - Photo Unit #: B400 Corporal Robert Nelson, Lincoln-Washington activist, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0177)
  - Photo Unit #: B402 Corporal Leo Markowitz, Lincoln-Washington activist, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0178)
  - Photo Unit #: B409 Lieutenant Richard Rusciano, Lincoln-Washington activist, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0179)
  - Photo Unit #: B414 John Tisa, Editor,Volunteer for Liberty, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0180)
  - Photo Unit #: B417 Frank Rogers, Commissar, MacKenzie-Papineau, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0181)
  - Photo Unit #: B418 Joseph Gibbons, MacKenzie-Papineau, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Apr 1938 (Item 11-0182)
  - Photo Unit #: B419 Joe Gibbons, MacKenzie-Papineau Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Apr 1938 (Item 11-1300)
  - Photo Unit #: B422 Corporal John Toutloff, MacKenzie-Papineau, Company 1, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0183)
  - Photo Unit #: B427 Corporal Carl Syvanen, Company 1, MacKenzie-Papineau, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0184)
  - Photo Unit #: B431 Gerald Glow, Practicante, Company 1, MacKenzie-Papineau, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0185)
  - Photo Unit #: B434 Lieutenant Jorge Carbonell, Company 1, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion (Cuban) in 15th International Brigade, May 1938 (Item 11-1301)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/40)
  - Photo Unit #: B435 Alejandro Masip, MacKenzie-Papineau, May 1938 (Item 11-0687)
  - Photo Unit #: B436 Carlos Arias, MacKenzie-Papineau, Company 1, activist, May 1938 (Item 11-0688)
  - Photo Unit #: B438 Lieutenant Harry Mack, Company 2, MacKenzie-Papineau, May 1938 (Item 11-1302)
  - Photo Unit #: B440 George Watt, Commissar, Lincoln-Washington, May 1938 (Item 11-0186)
  - Photo Unit #: B441 Lieutenant Howard Goddard, May 1938 (Item 11-0187)
  - Photo Unit #: B442 Edwin Rolfe, Cultural Director, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, May 1938 (Item 11-0188)
  - Photo Unit #: B443 Sergeant Eduardo, cook in British Battalion, May 1938 (Item 11-0016)
  - Photo Unit #: B449 Jose Bello, Brigade Comisariado [Commissariat] (youth organization), May 1938 (Item 11-0017)
  - Photo Unit #: B450 Alexander Goldberg, Commissar of Sanidad [Health], 15th International Brigade, May 1938 (Item 11-0018)
  - Photo Unit #: B451 Dr. Mark Straus, Chief of Sanidad [Health], 15th International Brigade, May 1938 (Item 11-0019)
  - Photo Unit #: B452 Dr. Mark Straus, Chief of Sanidad [Health], 15th International Brigade, May 1938 (Item 11-0020)
  - Photo Unit #: B456 Captain Rafael Brage, Servicio de Inteligencia Militar, 15th International Brigade, May 1938 (Item 11-0189)
  - Photo Unit #: B457 Lieutenant Ivan Rujevic, Servicio de Inteligencia Militar, 15th International Brigade, May 1938 (Item 11-0190)
  - Photo Unit #: B459 Roberto Buzon, activist (Cuban), May 1938 (Item 11-0191)
  - Photo Unit #: B462 Costas Scarlettos, activist, May 1938 (Item 11-0192)
  - Photo Unit #: B463 Arturo Ferrer, 59th Battalion activist, May 1938 (Item 11-0193)
  - Photo Unit #: B467 Pedro Ramos, activist, May 1938 (Item 11-0194)
  - Photo Unit #: B469 Manano Canavevas, activist, May 1938 (Item 11-0195)
  - Photo Unit #: B473 Roberto Beltran, activist, May 1938 (Item 11-0196)
  - Photo Unit #: B474 Antonio de Cardenas, activist, May 1938 (Item 11-0197)
  - Photo Unit #: B475 Armentien Ferias, activist, May 1938 (Item 11-0198)
  - Photo Unit #: B476 Manase Romero, activist, May 1938 (Item 11-0199)
  - Photo Unit #: B477 Felix Sanchez, 59th Battalion activist (Cuban), May 1938 (Item 11-0200)
  - Photo Unit #: B478 Corporal Jose Real, activist, May 1938 (Item 11-0201)
  - Photo Unit #: B479 Corporal Hector Morales, May 1938 (Item 11-0202)
  - Photo Unit #: B480 Luis Peraza, activist, May 1938 (Item 11-0203)
  - Photo Unit #: B481 Roland Cleveland, Practicante, Company 2, Lincoln-Washington, May 1938 (Item 11-0204)
  - Photo Unit #: B482 Charles Egun, Company 4, May 1938 (Item 11-0205)
  - Photo Unit #: B483 George Passoglou, Company 2, Lincoln-Washington, May 1938 (Item 11-0206)
  - Photo Unit #: B484 Constantine Dubac, May 1938 (Item 11-0207)
  - Photo Unit #: B489 Felix Sanchez Rego, 59th Battalion activist (Cuban), May 1938 (Item 11-0208)
  - Photo Unit #: B491 Herman Tabb, Lincoln-Washington, May 1938 (Item 11-0209)
  - Photo Unit #: B492 Valentin Koppel, Lincoln-Washington, May 1938 (Item 11-0210)
  - Photo Unit #: B493 [Soldier, unidentified], May 1938 (Item 11-0211)
  - Photo Unit #: B50 Sergeant Frank Proctor of anti-tank unit cited for bravery at Quinto and Belchite, Sep 1937 (Item 11-1797)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/8)
  - Photo Unit #: B500 Corporal Mack Coad, Company 2, MacKenzie-Papineau, May 1938 (Item 11-0212)
  - Photo Unit #: B501 Donald Livingstone, Company 2, MacKenzie-Papineau, May 1938 (Item 11-0213)
  - Photo Unit #: B504 Dr. Jose Dhaga, British Battalion, May 1938 (Item 11-0214)
  - Photo Unit #: B545 Dr. Julius Hene, Sanidad [Health], 15th International Brigade, May 1938 (Item 11-0215)
  - Photo Unit #: B546 Dr. Mark Straus, Sanidad [Health], 15th International Brigade, May 1938 (Item 11-0216)
  - Photo Unit #: B547 Nick J. Demas, Auto Park, May 1938 (Item 11-0021)
  - Photo Unit #: B548 Sergeant Harry Randall of the Photo Department, May 1938 (Item 11-0022)
  - Photo Unit #: B549 Corporal Harry C. Patterson, Company 1, MacKenzie-Papineau, May 1938 (Item 11-0023)
  - Photo Unit #: B550 Thomas Lloyd, Chauffeur, May 1938 (Item 11-1304)
  - Photo Unit #: B551 William Susman [alias Bill Ellis], May 1938 (Item 11-0024)
  - Photo Unit #: B553 Captain Radomir Smrcka, Chief of Information, May 1938 (Item 11-0025)
  - Photo Unit #: B554 Samuel Gonshak, Commissar of Auto Park, May 1938 (Item 11-0026)
  - Photo Unit #: B555 Isidore (Easy) Goldstein, Chief of "rolling" park, May 1938 (Item 11-0027)
  - Photo Unit #: B556 Isidore (Easy) Goldstein, Chief of "rolling" park, May 1938 (Item 11-0028)
  - Photo Unit #: B557 Saul Wellman, Commissar of Brigade Machine-Gunner Company, May 1938 (Item 11-0029)
  - Photo Unit #: B561 Edwin Rolfe, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, May 1938 (Item 11-0030)
  - Photo Unit #: B562 Edwin Rolfe, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, May 1938 (Item 11-0031)
  - Photo Unit #: B570 Jefferson Wideman of Vigilancia, 15th International Brigade, May 1938 (Item 11-0032)
  - Photo Unit #: B571 Lawrence Dukes, MacKenzie-Papineau, Company 1, May 1938 (Item 11-0033)
  - Photo Unit #: B572 Lawrence Dukes, MacKenzie-Papineau, Company 1, May 1938 (Item 11-0034)
  - Photo Unit #: B573 Lieutenant Solomon Rosenblum [alias Sol Rose], Adjuntant, MacKenzie-Papineau, May 1938 (Item 11-0035)
  - Photo Unit #: B574 Lieutenant Solomon Rosenblum [alias Sol Rose], Adjuntant, MacKenzie-Papineau, May 1938 (Item 11-0036)
  - Photo Unit #: B575 [James Patrick] Pat Murphy, May 1938 (Item 11-1305)
  - Photo Unit #: B576 Samuel Wren, May 1938 (Item 11-0217)
  - Photo Unit #: B592 Nathan Weisenfeld, May 1938 (Item 11-0218)
  - Photo Unit #: B594 John Petrullo, Pagaduria, May 1938 (Item 11-0219)
  - Photo Unit #: B595 Captain Leonard Lamb, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, May 1938 (Item 11-1306)
  - Photo Unit #: B596 Ben Barsky, MacKenzie-Papineau, May 1938 (Item 11-0220)
  - Photo Unit #: B597 John Murra, Lincoln-Washington, May 1938 (Item 11-0221)
  - Photo Unit #: B598 William (Red) Brown, Transmiciones [Transmissions], MacKenzie-Papineau, May 1938 (Item 11-0222)
  - Photo Unit #: B599 Captain David Kamy, May 1938 (Item 11-0969)
  - Photo Unit #: B600 Frank Rogers, Commissar, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, May 1938 (Item 11-0970)
    (Moscow Number: 5/188/86)
  - Photo Unit #: B601 David Davidson, Chauffeur, Auto Park, May 1938 (Item 11-0971)
  - Photo Unit #: B603 John Gates, 15th International Brigade Commissar, May 1938 (Item 11-0972)
  - Photo Unit #: B607 Alcorisa, Jan 1938 (Item 11-0689)
  - Photo Unit #: B610 Owen Smith of Operaciones [Operations], May 1938 (Item 11-0973)
  - Photo Unit #: B612 Sergeant Gerald Cook, Lincoln-Washington, May 1938 (Item 11-0223)
  - Photo Unit #: B613 Corporal Elman Service, Lincoln-Washington activist, May 1938 (Item 11-0224)
  - Photo Unit #: B614 Herman Tabb, Lincoln-Washington, May 1938 (Item 11-0225)
  - Photo Unit #: B615 Lieutenant Lionel Edwards, Company 1, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, May 1938 (Item 11-1307)
  - Photo Unit #: B622 Irving Gold, MacKenzie-Papineau, May 1938 (Item 11-0037)
  - Photo Unit #: B623 Paul George, chauffeur, Auto Park, May 1938 (Item 11-0038)
  - Photo Unit #: B624 Jack Steele, MacKenzie-Papineau Guard (returned Vet), May 1938 (Item 11-0039)
  - Photo Unit #: B627 [Soldier, unidentified], May 1938 (Item 11-0040)
  - Photo Unit #: B628 Efrain Guasch Leon, May 1938 (Item 11-0041)
  - Photo Unit #: B630 Vete Zablackas, Transmiciones [Transmissions], May 1938 (Item 11-0042)
  - Photo Unit #: B631 [African-American soldier], May 1938 (Item 11-0226)
  - Photo Unit #: B632 Walter Kolowski, returned to Lincoln-Washington Battalion from U.S., May 1938 (Item 11-0227)
  - Photo Unit #: B633 unidentified, May 1938 (Item 11-0974)
  - Photo Unit #: B634 Jose Antonio Valledor, Commander, 15th International Brigade, May 1938 (Item 11-1308)
  - Photo Unit #: B635 Jose Antonio Valledor, undated (Item 11-1309)
  - Photo Unit #: B638 Captain Milton Wolff, Lincoln-Washington, May 1938 (Item 11-0690)
  - Photo Unit #: B639 George Watt, Commissar, Lincoln-Washington Battalion [Image missing], May 1938 (Item 11-1854)
  - Photo Unit #: B645 Ramon Martinez Fernandez, undated (Item 11-1310)
  - Photo Unit #: B661 Milton Cohen, May 1938 (Item 11-0228)
  - Photo Unit #: B666 William Susman [alias Bill Ellis], May 1938 (Item 11-0229)
  - Photo Unit #: B679 Sandor Voros, Chief of Brigade Commissariat, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0975)
  - Photo Unit #: B681 Joseph Hecht, chauffeur of Commissariat, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1311)
  - Photo Unit #: B683 Arnold Reid, Commissar of Machine-Gunner Company 59th Battalion, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1312)
  - Photo Unit #: B684 Jose Antonio Valledor, Commander, 15th International Brigade, May 1938 (Item 11-0043)
  - Photo Unit #: B685 Steven Boleslaw, Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0044)
  - Photo Unit #: B686 Sandor Voros, Commissariat, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0045)
  - Photo Unit #: B691 Michael Pavlos, Lincoln-Washington Practicante, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0046)
  - Photo Unit #: B693 [Soldier, saluting], Jun 1938 (Item 11-0230)
  - Photo Unit #: B694 Sergeant Andrew Borysko, Sanidad [Health] transport, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1313)
  - Photo Unit #: B696 Sergeant Andrew Borysko, Sanidad [Health] transport, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0047)
  - Photo Unit #: B697 John Tisa, Editor, Volunteer for Liberty, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0048)
  - Photo Unit #: B699 Harry Hakam, Lincoln-Washington, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0049)
  - Photo Unit #: B700 Harry Hakam, Lincoln-Washington, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0050)
  - Photo Unit #: B704 Morris Goldstein, Company 1 Commissar, Lincoln-Washington, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0051)
  - Photo Unit #: B707 [Soldier, portrait], Jul 1938 (Item 11-0052)
  - Photo Unit #: B708 Sergeant Milton Cohen, Company 1, MacKenzie-Papineau, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0053)
  - Photo Unit #: B709 Thomas Page, Lincoln-Washington, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0231)
  - Photo Unit #: B710 Hyman Chesler, Lincoln-Washington, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0054)
  - Photo Unit #: B711 Kopel Koplowitz [alias Kaye Matthews], Intendente of Auto Park, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0055)
  - Photo Unit #: B712 Efrain Guasch, Adjuntant Commissar, 59th Battalion, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1314)
  - Photo Unit #: B715 Samuel Spiller, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0056)
  - Photo Unit #: B719 Sergeant Gerald Cook, Lincoln-Washington, Company 3 cited, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0057)
  - Photo Unit #: B720 Corporal Leonard Holtzclaw, Lincoln-Washington, Company 3 cited, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0058)
  - Photo Unit #: B721 Corporal Jack Barrett, Lincoln-Washington, Company 3 cited, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0059)
  - Photo Unit #: B723 Sandor Voros, Chief of Commissariat, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0060)
  - Photo Unit #: B724 Abraham Smorodin, MacKenzie-Papineau, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0232)
  - Photo Unit #: B725 Abraham Smorodin, MacKenzie-Papineau, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0233)
  - Photo Unit #: B726 David Gordon, Commissariat, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0234)
  - Photo Unit #: B728 Sandor Voros, Commissariat, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0235)
  - Photo Unit #: B729 Ernest Amatniek, Transmiciones [Transmissions], Aug 1938 (Item 11-0236)
  - Photo Unit #: B730 Ben Barsky, MacKenzie-Papineau, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0237)
  - Photo Unit #: B731 John O'Hara, MacKenzie-Papineau, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0238)
  - Photo Unit #: B732 Harry Schoenberg, MacKenzie-Papineau, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0239)
  - Photo Unit #: B734 Antonio Pujol, Comisariado [Commissariat], Sep 1938 (Item 11-0240)
  - Photo Unit #: B736 David (Red) Drummond, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0061)
  - Photo Unit #: B737 Harry Hakam, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0062)
  - Photo Unit #: B738 Lieutenant David Smith, Company 4, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0241)
  - Photo Unit #: B739 Lieutenant David Smith, Company 4, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0242)
  - Photo Unit #: B740 Lieutenant William Wheeler, Company 4, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0243)
  - Photo Unit #: B741 Lawrence Lustgarten, undated (Item 11-1315)
  - Photo Unit #: B742 Borzidor Dakic, special Machine-Gunner Company (Yugoslav), Sep 1938 (Item 11-0244)
  - Photo Unit #: B743 Benjamin (Butch) Goldstein, MacKenzie-Papineau, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0245)
  - Photo Unit #: B744 Ernst Lesser, Commissariat, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0246)
  - Photo Unit #: B745 Benito Rodriguez, chauffeur, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0247)
  - Photo Unit #: B746 Jacob Elias Cohen, oficina, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0248)
  - Photo Unit #: B750 Armando Torres Diaz, Commissariat, 59th Brigade, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0249)
  - Photo Unit #: B751 Constantino Dubas, Adjuntant Commissar, 59th Brigade, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0250)
  - Photo Unit #: B754 Archie Brown, Commissar, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0251)
  - Photo Unit #: B755 Melchor Rajon, Commissar, Company 1, 59th Battalion, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0252)
    Available Formats: Original Negative
  - Photo Unit #: B761 Lawrence Cohen [alias Larry Cane], Commissar, Company 1, 59th Battalion, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0253)
  - Photo Unit #: B762 Carlos Arias, Commissar, Company 1, 59th Battalion, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0254)
  - Photo Unit #: B764 Sergeant Louis Gayle, Sanidad [Health], Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0255)
  - Photo Unit #: B766 David Doran, Jan 1937 (Item 11-0691)
- Series C: Group Portraits, September 1937-August 1938.
  Series IIC: Group Portraits, September 1937 - August 1938, consists of 259 images, which range from double portraits of volunteers casually posing to more formal group photos of entire units. Included here are the Lincoln Washington Machine-Gunner Company, officers of British Anti-Tank Unit, the 15th International Brigade Transmiciones (the unit in charge of communication or transmission); the 24th Spanish Battalion Machine-Gunner Company; the motor cyclists of 15th Brigade; the Lincoln-Washington ambulance and medical personnel; Earl Browder and officers of the 15th International Brigade; Greeks in the Lincoln Battalion; an African-American machine-gunner crew; Doctor Edward Barsky and a medical colleague; Captain Leonard Lamb with Lieutenant William Digges; and five New York University students -- volunteers with the Abraham Lincoln Brigade.
  - Photo Unit #: C001 Lincoln-Washington food truck at Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0692)